spoyl.in 2018-12-21

# Spoyl | Fashion Influencer-led Online Shopping for Men & Women in India

_shopping_cart_

The application spoyl is brought to you by Spoyl Tech Solutions Pvt Ltd. Spoyl tech solutions private limited (“spoyl,” “we,” and “us”) respects the privacy of its users (“you”) and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our application or services or transacting business with us. By using our website or mobile application (our “Service”), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

1\. Information we collect about you 

  * In General. We may collect information that can identify you such as your name and email address, mobile number ("personal information") and other information that does not identify you. We may collect this information through a website or a mobile application. By using the Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse and retain data related to the provision of the Service. 
    * Information you provide. In order to register as a user with spoyl, you will be asked to sign in using your Facebook login as an option. If you do so, you authorize us to access certain Facebook account information, such as your public Facebook profile (consistent with your privacy settings in Facebook), your email address, interests, likes, gender, birthday, education history, relationship interests, current city, photos, personal description, friend list, and information about and photos of your Facebook friends who might be common Facebook friends with other spoyl users. 
    * In addition, we may collect and store any personal information you provide while using our Service or in some other manner. This may include identifying information, such as your name, address, email address and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information. Data you provide about your favourite products/brand/stores, all social data, chat data, all browsing data, purchasing data, poll data and wishlist data to make suggestions of products that suit your tastes. 
    * This data is held securely and we only provide it to partners to improve their offerings to you and never do so without making the data untraceable and anonymous. We also use personal data when carrying out statistical analysis of spoyl users behaviour and to create anonymised statistical data which we may use at our discretion (including licensing to third parties). If you contact us with a customer service or other inquiry, you provide us with the content of that communication. 

  * Use of technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to collect information from your device and about your activities on our Service. 
    * Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser or device when you visit our Service. This information could include your IP address, device ID and type, your browser type and language, the operating system used by your device, access times, your mobile device’s geographic location while our application is actively running, and the linking/referring website address. 
    * Cookies and Use of Cookie Data. When you visit our Service, we may assign your device one or more cookies to facilitate access to our Service and to personalize your experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your activity on our Service, such as the pages you visit, the time and date of your visits and the links you click. If we advertise, we (or third parties) may use certain data collected on our Service to show you spoyl advertisements on other sites or applications. 
    * Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our Service and to deliver or communicate with cookies. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or email messages to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer users, to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities. 
    * Information collected by third-parties for advertising purposes. We may allow service providers, advertising companies and ad networks, and other third parties to display advertisements on our Service. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. We do not provide any non-anonymized personal information to third parties. 

2\. How we use the information we collect 

  * In General. We may use information that we collect about you to: 
    * Deliver and improve our products and services, and manage our business;
    * Manage your account and provide you with customer support; 
    * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our or others’ products, services, or content; 
    * Communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties; 
    * Develop, display, and track content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Service and other sites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other sites; 
    * Website or mobile application analytics; 
    * Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes; 
    * Enforce or exercise any rights in our Terms of Use; and Perform functions or services as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 

  * Job applicants. If your personal information is submitted through our website when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used solely in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may retain your personal information, but only for the purpose of considering your application for current or future available positions. This information, which may include your name and contact information, prior education and experience, and other information you provide to us, may be shared with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings. 

  * In all circumstances, we may perform these functions directly or use a third party vendor to perform these functions on our behalf who will be obligated to use your personal information only to perform services for us. Also, if you access our Service from a third party social platform, such as Facebook, we may share non-personal information with that platform to the extent permitted by your agreement with it and its privacy settings. 

3\. With whom we share your information

  * Information Shared with Other Users. When you register as a user of spoyl, your spoyl profile will be viewable by other users of the Service, mainly during using spoyl’s instant chat options. If you chat with a friend/family member using spoyl, of course your friend/family member will see the content of your chat. 

  * Service providers: We may share information, including personal and financial information, with third parties that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, ad tracking and analytics, member screenings, supporting our Service functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Service. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes. 
  *     * Aggregated and/or non-personal information. We may use and share non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Service and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non- personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated, non-personal information, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis or other business purposes. 

  * Job applicants. If your personal information is submitted through our website when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used solely in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may retain your personal information, but only for the purpose of considering your application for current or future available positions. This information, which may include your name and contact information, prior education and experience, and other information you provide to us, may be shared with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings. 

  * In all circumstances, we may perform these functions directly or use a third party vendor to perform these functions on our behalf who will be obligated to use your personal information only to perform services for us. Also, if you access our Service from a third party social platform, such as Facebook, we may share non-personal information with that platform to the extent permitted by your agreement with it and its privacy settings. 

4\. How you can access your information

If you have a spoyl account, you have the ability to review and update your personal information within the Service by opening your account and going to settings. More information about how to contact us is provided below. You also may close your account at any time by visiting the "Settings" page for your account. If you close your account, we will retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, enforce our Terms of Use, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our Service or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies. 

5\. Partners we work with

We work with a range of partners to track the sales generated via spoyl application. This is to ensure we can claim commission from our partners for generating sales for them and to make your online shopping experience as positive as possible. The partners we work with range from individual stores/brands, large affiliate networks, data networks and others. These partners work with us via cookies and other tracking links and methods. At no point is your personal data available to any partners and you’re always treated anonymously. 

6\. Your choices about collection and use of your information

* You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Service because such information may be required in order for you to register as user; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions. 
* Our Service may also deliver notifications to your phone or mobile device. You can disable these notifications by deleting the relevant Service or by changing the settings on your mobile device. 
* You can also control information collected by cookies. You can delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. Click “help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions. 

7\. How we protect your personal information

We take security measures to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, chats, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. 

8\. Information you provide about yourself while using our Service

We provide areas on our Service where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use . Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting (chats) or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. 

9\. No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website. 

10\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Service from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies. 

11\. How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at care@spoyl.in
